etundra.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy | eTundra

Date of Last Revision: March 6, 2013

This policy covers how Tundra Restaurant Supply (“Tundra”) treats collected personal information, including information related to the use of our products and services. This privacy statement discloses Tundra practices for the gathering and use of information from visitors to [www.etundra.com](http://www.etundra.com/) (the “Website”), from people who register and use our online services. This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Tundra does not own or control, or to people that Tundra does not explicitly employ or manage.

**Table of Contents**

  1. Information Collection and Use
  2. Registration
  3. Order and Application
  4. Refer a Friend
  5. Special Offers and Promotions
  6. Service-Related Announcements
  7. Customer Service
  8. Profile Information
  9. ID and Address Verification
  10. Personally Identifiable Info
  11. Agents and Service Providers
  12. Legal Disclaimer
  13. Choice/Opt Out
  14. Log Files 
  15. Cookies
  16. Links to Other Sites
  17. Security
  18. Business Transitions
  19. Privacy Policy Changes
  20. Contact Information

**1\. Information Collection and Use**

Tundra is committed to personal privacy and has adopted a stringent policy to show our dedication towards safeguarding information collection and use. Tundra is the primary owner of the information collected on our domain(s).

**We guarantee we will not sell or rent collected information. Tundra may share certain information (only where appropriate) with individuals and businesses responsible for handling your account or performing other services that you require.**

Tundra collects information for the following general purposes:

  * Contacting Registrants
  * Personalizing User Experience
  * Fulfilling Requests as Specified
  * Security and Authorization
  * Monitoring and Logging Activity
  * Billing, Shipping, and Processing
  * Account Administration
  * Improving Service Delivery
  * Anonymous Research and Reporting

**2\. Registration**

In order to better serve you, at various points you may complete a registration form voluntarily. During the registration process you may be required to provide contact information (such as name, phone number, email address, etc.). This information is to be used for the sole purpose of providing you with additional information that pertains to the interest(s) specified during your registration. Members who opt to use our services will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, etc. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we always present the option to be removed from these types of communications.

**3\. Order and Application Forms**

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

**4\. Refer a Friend**

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Tundra stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us to request that we remove this information from our database.

**5\. Special Offers and Promotions**

We will occasionally send you information on products, special deals and promotions. You can sign up for these emails from us on our registration page.

Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out.”

**6\. Service-Related Announcements**

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

**7\. Customer Service**

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

**8\. Profile Information**

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, [and/or third party sources] to create a “profile” of your preferences. We tie your personally identifiable information, and your purchasing history, to information in the profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site for you.

We may share certain information (only where appropriate) with individuals and businesses responsible for handling your account or performing other services that you require.

**9\. ID and Address Verification**

We use third party services to verify your identity and address, in order to protect against theft and fraud.

**10\. Personally Identifiable Information**

We share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties only when necessary to perform the services that you explicitly request. Information may be used to verify your identity, fulfill a purchase or provide customer service.

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change in the My Account section, by emailing our Customer Support, or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail.

**11\. Agents and Service Providers**

We use an outside shipping company to fulfill orders, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

The following is a list of third party providers that we use:

  * [Data393](http://www.data393.com/) E-Business Platform
  * [Verisign](http://www.verisign.com/) Payment Processing
  * [Comodo Group](http://www.comodogroup.com/) Secure Certificate (SSL)

These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. Please visit the website for each provider to learn more about their privacy practices.

**12\. Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website.

**13\. Choice/Opt-Out**

We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by contacting us.

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

**14\. Log Files**

As is true of most Websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click-stream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information to help prevent theft and fraud and to provide the customer with a personalized experience.

We use a third-party tracking service that uses cookies and log files to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site.

**15\. Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.

We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. The use of cookies are necessary to conduct ecommerce on our website.

**16\. Links to Other Sites**

This Website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Tundra. Please be aware that we, Tundra, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Website that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Website.

**17\. Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). When registration forms (i.e. ecommerce) require a user to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), the information is encrypted and protected with the best encryption standard in the industry—SSL. The information collected is to be used for billing purposes and to fulfill the customer’s orders. While on a secure page, such as an ecommerce website, a lock icon is present at the bottom of the Web browser (for Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer) indicating the information transmitted will be encrypted. To learn more about SSL, please visit http://webopedia.internet.com/term/s/ssl.html. To check the validity of the SSL certificate, please be sure to click on the lock icon located at the bottom of your browser window.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Website, you can contact us.

**18\. Business Transitions**

In the event Tundra goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email or a prominent notice on our Website within 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

**19\. Changes in this Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

**20\. Contact Information**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
